Guide to the Samuel Slie Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
Samuel Slie Papers
1961-1986
RG 111
Yale University Divinity School Library
30
(67 boxes)
This collection documents Samuel Slie's work with numerous organizations involved in student Christian work, ecumenical issues, and social justice, particularly in New Haven and New England. The papers complement organizational archives held at the Yale Divinity School Library, including the archives of the Student Christian Movement in New England, University Christian Movement, United Ministries in Higher Education, and National Campus Ministry Association. Samuel Slie, a Yale Divinity School graduate, was involved in religious work with college and university students in New England and served as Associate University Pastor at Yale.
Slie, Samuel
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Samuel Slie
Biographical / Historical
Reverend Samuel Slie was born in Branford, Connecticut on June 8, 1925. Since his childhood he has been affiliated with the United Church of Christ (UCC) into which he was ordained in 1952. He graduated from Hillhouse High School, was a veteran of the infantry service in World War II after which he obtained his B.S. in Group Work and Community Organization from Springfield College in Massachusetts. He also studied at Wilberforce University in Ohio and overseas in Florence, Italy. In 1952 he received his B.D. in Religion and Higher Education and in 1963 a S.T.M in Roman Catholic Ecumenical Thought fromYale Divinity School.
Befitting his education, Rev. Slie has held many positions which placed him at the center of the dialogue between religion and higher education and interfaith/ecumenical thought. He began at the Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) for which he became the Southern Area Secretary of the National Student Council in 1952. In 1955 he became the Regional Director of the New England Student Christian Movement (SCM) for the United Church of Christ, a position he held for ten years until 1965. The position which led him into closer contact with Yale was the Coordinating Chaplain of the United Ministry in Higher Education in Greater New Haven, which he began in 1965. His work there was as a campus ministry liaison and resource person on an ecumenical basis among the seven colleges of Greater New Haven. His accomplishments in this position were endorsed by the New Haven Council of Churches. In January of 1966 he also became the Associate University Pastor, Yale University, Church of Christ (part-time) and a Fellow of Morse College. From 1969 through 1975 he was part-time lecturer at Yale Divinity School. He lectured on: The Church and the Black Experience, Women in Campus Ministry, and Christian Ministry in Higher Education.
As a resource person and a pastor he was required to be current on a variety of issues from religious, to social, to intellectual. He was affiliated with the Danforth Foundation and the Ministries to Blacks in Higher Education, was knowledgeable of the New Haven Pagan Council, concerned about famine in South Africa, and desired the flourishing of Christian Unity. Despite his knowledge of and frequent offers to work for secular institutions he consistently chose the institutional church. His theological grounding and faith were repeatedly praised by a variety of people. His ministry has been most appropriately described as a ministry of reconciliation where both judgment and healing can occur.
Scope and Contents
This collection provides valuable biographical information about Slie as well as documenting the numerous organizations and issues that were of interest to Slie during his long career as a prominent African American religious leader in the New Haven area. Much of the collection consists of writings and printed material related to the various issues that concerned Slie, but there are also writings and correspondence by Slie. Taken in conjunction with relevant organizational archives held at the Yale Divinity School Library, these papers provide insight into the volatile era of the 1960s and 1970s in New England, a time of great change for student Christian work and society in general.
The 2010 Addendum consists of Slie's "working file" of materials related to various organizations and issues of interest to him.
Arrangement
I. Religion in Higher Education
II. Social Justice
III. Interfaith and Ecumenical Dialogue
IV. Yale Connections
V. Personal
VI. Addendum - 2010
Church work with students; Universities and colleges -- United States -- Religion; Clergy; Slie, Samuel, 1925-; Student Christian Movement in New England; United Ministries in Higher Education; Yale University. Divinity School
- Religion in Higher Education, Series I
  - Organizations
    - ANRC: The American Red Cross Collection: "The University in the Changing Community: New Directions in Social Responsibility" by Wesley P. Lloyd, "Education for Social Responsibility" by Philip E. Jacob, "Profile of a College Student by College Students", 1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - BCM: Hana and Black College Ministers Convocation (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - CCC: Christian Conference of CT CT Council of Churches (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - CCMA: Catholic Campus Ministry Association Newsletter, 1975,1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - CCMA: Catholic Campus Ministry Association Study Week/Winter Workshop at Barry College (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - CMHE: Cambridge Ministry in Higher Education Newsletters, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - CMPE: Committee on Ministry in Public Education (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Danforth Foundation: correspondence and Annual Reports, 1964,1974 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Danforth Foundation: News Notes (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Danforth Foundation: Study concerning ministry in Higher Education (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Dartmouth--The Dartmouth Christian Union (2 copies), correspondence and news concerning the Tucker Foundation (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - DCM: Downtown Cooperative Ministry (Box 2, Folder 13-15)
    - Second and Third Ecumenical Campus Ministry Conference, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - FCM: Faculty Christian Movement "Faculty Forum", 1964-1974 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Koinonia: "Practical Religion or The Sermon on the Mount and The Epistle of James" the Koinonia "Cotton Patch" version, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - MBHE: Ministries to Blacks in Higher Education (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - MBHE: Toward Wholeness--A journal of Ministries to Blacks in Higher Education, 1972-1985 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - NACUC: National Association of College and University Chaplains and Directors of Religious Life (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - NBCSC: National Black Christian Students Conference, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - NCCC: National Council of Churches in Christ Higher Education News Notes (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - NCCC (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - NCCC: Conference on Moral/Values and Education (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - NCCC: Together in Young Adult Ministry (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - NCCM: National Center for Campus Ministry (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - NCCJ: National Conference of Christians and Jews "And Crown thy Good: A Manual on Interreligious Cooperation on the College Campus" (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - NCMA: National Campus Ministry Association (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - NCMA: Newsletter, 1975-1985 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - NESCC: National Ecumenical Student Christian Council (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - NESCC: Advisory Council (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - NESCC: Planning Committee (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - NESCC: NIC (interim council) (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - NICM: National Institute for Campus Ministries Conference on Ministry Through Community (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - NNN: National Newman News, 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - NSCF: National Sutdent Christian Federation "Communique", 1962 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - NSCF: Collection: "Rediscovering the Church: A Study Guide for Lesslie Newbigin's Book 'The Household of God'" by Eugene S. Wehrli, "Study-Strategy Guide on the theme: For the Life of the World," "Ecumenical Development Among Christian Students" (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Ombudsmanry (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - OS: Overseas Students (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Pembroke Alumna, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - REA: Religious Education Association (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - SCM: Student Christian Movement (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - SEC: Sunday Evening Club--New Haven (succeeded by United Student Fellowship) (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Taizé, 1970-1979 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - TFRC: Tucker Foundation Review Committee (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - UCB: University of California-Berkeley "The Research Reporter, 1970-1975 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - UCC: United Church of Christ published materials (Box 6, Folder 48-49)
    - UCC (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - UCCF: United Campus Christian Fellowship publications, Metropolitan Ministry, and reports (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - UCM: University Christian Movement (Box 7, Folder 52-54)
    - UCM (Box 8, Folder 55-56)
    - UMC: United Methodist Church publications (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - UME: United Ministries in Education (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - UMHE: United Ministries in Higher Education records, constitution, activities, and plans (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - UMHE: Advisory Board (New Haven) (Box 9, Folder 61-65)
    - UMHE: Collection: Resource Index, "So There's a Community College in Your Town: A Guide for Local Church Ministry With the Nearby Community College" ed. by W.E. Hallman, "True Family: Korean Communitarianism and American Loneliness" by Leo Sandon, Jr., "Radical Directions in Higher Education, 1973-1978 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - UMHE: Papers: Church and Community College #5 "After the Boom...What now for Community Colleges," #6 "The Local Church and the Community College," #7 "A Case Method Approach to Developing a Ministry with Community Colleges, " "Report of a Planning Study of the United Ministries in Higher Education" (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - UMHE: "Probe", 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - UMHE: Self-studies (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - UMHE: "Campus Ministry Bulletin", 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - UMHE Policy Paper (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - USF: United Student Federation (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - USF Financial Records 1962-66, 1962-1966 (Box 10, Folder 73-76)
    - WFGNH: Wesley Foundation of Greater New Haven, Inc. Financial Report, Organizational Material, Correspondence, Insurance and Mortgage information on 272 Canner St., and various minutes (Box 11, Folder 77-78)
    - WSCF: World Student Christian Federation Minutes of the 25th Meeting of the General Assembly of the WSCF, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - WSCF Journal (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - WSCF with connections to YCGJ Young Christians for Global Justice, UCM University Christian Movement, and SCM Student Christian Movement (Box 11, Folder 81)
    - WSCF (Box 11, Folder 82-83)
    - WUS: World University Service (Box 12, Folder 84-86)
    - YCS Young Christian Students: YCS Bulletin--National Journal of the College Young Christian Students Movement, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 87)
    - YMCA Young Men's Christian Association (Box 12, Folder 88-89)
    - YMCA (Box 13, Folder 90-91)
    - YMCA: Christian Emphasis Retreat and Christian Commitment Task Force (Box 13, Folder 92)
    - YMCA: Energy for the 80's--National Council of YMCA Northeast Region (Box 13, Folder 93)
    - YMCA: From Gesture to Commitment (Box 13, Folder 94)
    - YMCA: International Division Assembly (Box 13, Folder 95)
    - YMCA/YWCA Collection: "Program Planning for Student YMCAs and YWCAs," "Dialogue on Campus..." by Nelle Morton, "Organization of Student YMCAs and Student Christian Associations," "Behold the Man: Meditation on the Meaning of the Cross," "Young men and Young Women: New Insights on Becoming an Adult" by Allen S. Ellsworth (Box 13, Folder 96)
    - Yoke Fellowship (Box 14, Folder 97)
  - Miscellaneous
    - "As I See it Today" by Moffett Duart Swaim, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 98)
    - "Christian Identity on Campus" by Myron B. Bloy, Jr. (Box 14, Folder 99)
    - "Church and Campus in Pennsylvania" (Box 14, Folder 100)
    - "Five Experiments in Campus Christian Community", 1962 (Box 14, Folder 101)
    - "Improvement of Opportunity in Higher Education" report to CT Gov. (Box 14, Folder 102)
    - "The Church and the University" by Jacques De Senarclens (Box 14, Folder 103)
    - "The College Student in an Age of Organization" by David Riesman (Box 14, Folder 104)
    - "The Role of the Church in Higher Education" by Samuel Slie (Box 14, Folder 105)
    - "The University and the Church" by Harold K. Schilling (Box 14, Folder 106)
    - "The Word The Church and The University" by George H. Williams, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 107)
    - "Viewpoints on Higher Education" The Report of a Study of the Attitudes of Pennsylvanians Toward Higher Education (Box 14, Folder 108)
    - Addresses given in Dwight Memorial Chapel, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 109)
    - Articles related to Campus Ministry (Box 14, Folder 110)
    - Campus Ministry Journals and Papers (Box 14, Folder 111)
    - Papers on Church and College (Box 14, Folder 112)
    - Connecticut Conference--Congregational Churches "Missioner", 1975 (Box 15, Folder 113)
    - Dissertation: "Evangelical Academy and Parish in West Germany" by Lee J. Gamble, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 114)
    - Pamphlets, newsletters, correspondence--various campus ministry organizations (Box 15, Folder 115)
    - Papers 1-7 of Church, University, and Urban Society project: "The Church, the University, and Urban Society: A Problem in Power," "The Church...:Focus on the Church," "The Church...:Implications for the University," "The Power of Development: Some Possibilities We See," "Urban Curricula and the Liberal Arts College," "Action-Research: A New Style of Politics, Education," "The Public Life: Its decline and Renewal" (Box 15, Folder 116)
    - Papers 1-8 Master Plan for Higher Education in Connecticut (Box 15, Folder 117)
    - Papers on Campus Ministry (Box 16, Folder 118)
    - Resource Lists (Box 16, Folder 119)
    - Seminars (Box 16, Folder 120)
    - Various Pamphlets, newsletters and journals (Box 16, Folder 121)
- Social Justice, Series II
  - Organizations
    - AFRO: African Famine Relief Organization (Box 16, Folder 122)
    - AFSC: American Friends Service Committee--Overseas Work Camps (Box 16, Folder 123)
    - AID: Association for International Development "Dialogue", 1963 (Box 16, Folder 124)
    - ARFEP: Americans for Reappraisal of Far Eastern Policies (Box 16, Folder 125)
    - CFC: Campus-Free College: Resource Guides Journal issues (Box 16, Folder 126)
    - CIDOC: Centro Intercultural de Documentacion, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 127)
    - Connect: Aging and Environmental issues (Box 16, Folder 128)
    - CVSA: Commission on Voluntary Service and Action (Box 16, Folder 129)
    - Free School University (Box 16, Folder 130)
    - Hazen Foundation (Box 16, Folder 131)
    - Jesus People (Box 16, Folder 132)
    - Koinonia (Box 16, Folder 133)
    - MRSJ: Ministers for Racial and Social Justice (Box 16, Folder 134)
    - NCBC: National Committee of Black Churchmen (Box 16, Folder 135)
    - NYS: New York State Offers Careers in Social Work (Box 17, Folder 136)
    - Planned Parenthood--Population issues (Box 17, Folder 137)
    - PSCA: Priests Social Action Committee "The Servant Church?", 1970 (Box 17, Folder 138)
    - SDS: Students for a Democratic Society (Box 17, Folder 139)
    - Tutoring--Yale/New Haven Tutorial Reading Program (Box 17, Folder 140)
    - UCBWM: United Church Board for World Ministries (Box 17, Folder 141)
    - UN: United Nations Day, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 142-143)
    - UN (Box 18, Folder 144)
    - Wind Chaff, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 145)
    - WSCF: Collection: "65 Years of Tradition," "Vietnam: A Symposium of International University Opinion," "Trying Times: American Politics in Transition from the Sixties to the Seventies, " "The Fourth Man and the Gospel" by Josef Smolik, WSCF Journal no. 0 (Box 18, Folder 146)
    - YCGJ: Young Christians for Global Justice (Box 18, Folder 147)
  - Miscellaneous
    - "A Proposal to the National Endowment for the Humanities for a Development Grant for 1975-1980" St. Olaf College, Northfield, MN Dr. David L. Wee, Principle Investigator, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 148)
    - "A Time to Choose: South Africa" (Box 18, Folder 149)
    - "Catholic Students and Political Involvement" by Mary Varela (Box 18, Folder 150)
    - "New World" Toward our Third Century: 120 Events Illuminating the Past, Present and Future of America, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 151)
    - "The Activist" (Box 18, Folder 152)
    - "The Future is in our Hands" (Box 18, Folder 153)
    - "The Sin of Anti-Semitism: Statements by Christian Churches" (Box 18, Folder 154)
    - "The Student Guide to Sex on Campus" by The Student Committee on Human Sexuality Yale University (Box 18, Folder 155)
    - A National Conference on The Church and the City (Box 18, Folder 156)
    - Africa News (Box 18, Folder 157)
    - Change, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 158)
    - Cross Currents "The Incomplete Revolution: A Reassessment of Recent Reforms in Higher Education" by Patrick J. Hill (Box 19, Folder 159)
    - Entropy (Box 19, Folder 160)
    - Folder on South Africa (Box 19, Folder 161)
    - Folder on World Hunger (Box 19, Folder 162)
    - Intercom (Box 19, Folder 163)
    - Jewish Relations (Box 19, Folder 164)
    - New Morality, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 165)
    - Peace folder (Box 19, Folder 166)
    - Sermon "In a Time of Tragic Conflict" by Dr. R.L. Shinn, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 167)
    - Social Concern pamphlets, papers, journals newsletters--mostly civil rights and Vietnam (Box 19, Folder 168)
    - Social Concern Issues (Box 20, Folder 169)
    - Teaching-Learning Issues "Proposal to Increase Value Consideration in our Curricula", 1975 (Box 20, Folder 170)
    - The Bioethics Letter: A Monthly Report on Ethical, Social and Legal Issues in Health Care and the Life Sciences, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 171)
    - The Haystack Prayer Meeting (Box 20, Folder 172)
    - The Liberal Context, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 173)
    - Theological and Philosophical Collection (Box 20, Folder 174)
    - University--Student Protests (Box 20, Folder 175)
    - Women vs. Connecticut (Box 20, Folder 176)
    - Women's Issues (Box 20, Folder 177-178)
    - Women's Issues (Box 21, Folder 179)
- Interfaith and Ecumenical Dialogue, Series III
  - Organizations
    - CIC: Catholic Interracial Council (Box 21, Folder 180)
    - COCU: Consultation on Church Union: The Reports of the Four Meetings (Box 21, Folder 181)
    - Crux, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 182)
    - Eastern Churches Quarterly: An Ecumenical Catholic Quarterly (Box 21, Folder 183)
    - ECEC: Ecumenical Continuing Education Center (Box 21, Folder 184)
    - Encounter: A Catholic-Jewish Confrontation (Box 21, Folder 185)
    - Liturgy: Bulletin of the Liturgical Conference, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 186)
    - Mediation, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 187)
    - Newman Apostolate Newsletter, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 188)
    - NHP: New Haven Pagan Council--Occult (Box 21, Folder 189)
    - OCF: Orthodox Christian Fellowship newsletter, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 190)
    - Pax Romana Journal, 1964-1966 (Box 21, Folder 191)
    - PMC: Packard Manse Collection (Box 21, Folder 192)
    - SAP: "An Adventure in Ecumenism" "Democracy and Dynamics of Change" by the Ecumenical Christian Center Bangalore (Box 21, Folder 193)
    - Teilhard Review (Box 21, Folder 194)
    - UC: Unification Church "The Character of Unification Theology as a Modern Christian Statement" by Dr. Thomas Boslooper (Box 21, Folder 195)
    - UC: "The Cornerstone", 1978-84 (Box 21, Folder 196)
    - UC: Newsletter (Box 21, Folder 197)
    - WCC: World Council of Churches (Box 21, Folder 198)
    - WCC: World Council of Churches (Box 22, Folder 199-202)
    - Youth, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 203)
  - Miscellaneous
    - "A Time to Rend and a Time to Sew: A Sermon on the Second Vatican Council" by Rev. Prof. George Huntston Williams (Box 22, Folder 204)
    - "Reflections on Pacem In Terris" by Mary Elizabeth Taylor (Box 22, Folder 205)
    - "The Religious Freedom Record" (Box 22, Folder 206)
    - "Towards a Secular Understanding of the Ecumenical?" An Occasional Study Paper by Albert H. van den Heuvel (Box 22, Folder 207)
    - "What can a Jew Believe About Jesus and Still Remain a Jew?" by Markus Barth (Box 22, Folder 208)
    - Agape (Box 22, Folder 209)
    - Christian Unity (Box 22, Folder 210)
    - Collection of Selected Bibliographies (Box 22, Folder 211)
    - Ecumenical Newsletter: An Occasional newsletter Published by Catholic, Orthodox, and Protestant Students, 1964-1966 (Box 22, Folder 212)
    - From the Desk of the Director Stanley I. Stuber, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 213)
    - Sensitivity Groups (Box 23, Folder 214)
    - Sheed and Ward's Own Trumpet, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 215)
    - The Challenge, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 216)
    - Week of Prayer for Christian Unity (Box 23, Folder 217)
- Yale Connections, Series IV
  - Westminster Foundation at Yale (connected to Wayne Meeks): budget (Box 23, Folder 218)
  - WF at Yale: Call and resignation of Wayne Meeks and reports by Wayne Meeks (Box 23, Folder 219)
  - WF: Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 220)
  - WF: Evaluation (Box 23, Folder 221)
  - WF: Fellowship (Box 23, Folder 222)
  - WF: Minutes before 1965 (Box 23, Folder 223)
  - Presbyterian Ministry at Yale Advisory Committee (Box 24, Folder 224)
  - Presbyterian Ministry Reports (Box 24, Folder 225)
  - WF PM misc. (Box 24, Folder 226)
  - Slie's Course Materials (Box 24, Folder 227)
  - YDS Alumni Council (Box 24, Folder 228)
  - YDS Course Listings (Box 24, Folder 229)
  - YDS Field-Based Education (Box 24, Folder 230)
- Personal Items, Series V
  - Collection of Job Description (Box 24, Folder 231)
  - Collection of Meeting/committee notes (no order) (Box 24, Folder 232)
  - Collection of Poetry by Rip Avann (Box 24, Folder 233)
  - Collection of Religious Services (Box 24, Folder 234)
  - College Cevenol (Box 24, Folder 235)
  - Employment Information (Box 24, Folder 236)
  - Miscellaneous Materials (No Order): correspondence, reports and personal notes (Box 25, Folder 237-239)
  - Northeast Regional Ecumenical Evangelical Conference (Mostly Bios--Slie's included) (Box 25, Folder 240)
  - Selection Committee Notes (Box 25, Folder 241)
  - Filmstrip and Record Album, Posters (Box 26)
- Addendum - 2010, Series VI
  - A
    - Addresses (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Africa (see also "South Africa," "Coalition Against Apartheid," "Course-Related") (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - African Famine Relief (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Agape retreat center, Italy, 1977-1983 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Albertus Magnus College, 1965-1972 (Box 27, Folder 5-6)
    - American Friends Service Committee (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Association of Yale Alumni (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Battell Chapel / Church of Christ at Yale
    - Annual Reports (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Baptisms (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Benevolence and Social Action (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Christian Education Program (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Communion (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Constitution and Bylaws (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Council (Box 28, Folder 8-9)
    - Crisis in the Nation relief effort (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Deacons (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Directory (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Finances (Box 29, Folder 4-5)
    - General Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - General (Box 29, Folder 7-8)
    - New Members (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Newsletters (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Nomination Committee (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Pastors (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Renovation and Maintenance (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Sermons by Slie and reports by John Vannorsdall (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Services of Worship, 1965-1975 (Box 30, Folder 1-5)
    - Services of Worship, 1976-1986, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 1-3)